https://cpp.canon/terms/

You are here: Home1 / Terms of useTerms and Conditions of Use
PLEASE READ THIS DOCUMENT BEFORE ACCESSING THE WEBSITE OF CANON PRODUCTION PRINTING. BY ACCESSING THE WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS. IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, DO NOT USE THE WEBSITE.
1. Acceptance
We, our affiliates and resellers, provide you with access to this web site (the “Website”) and through the Website to our available information, documents, images, software and/or products (collectively, “Materials”) and/or various services operated by or for us (collectively, “Services”), subject to the following terms and conditions (“Terms and Conditions”).
By accessing or using the Website you agree to be legally bound by these Terms and Conditions.
These Terms and Conditions may be updated by us from time to time by posting the updated Terms and Conditions without prior separate notification to you. You should check the Terms and Conditions each time you access the Website to check for updates.
2. Website
You will be able to access available Materials and/or various Services operated by or for us on the Website. As the case may be, you may also submit queries to us to receive more information. Please note that the Materials and Services might vary from country to country. Please contact your local Canon organization if you desire to find out details about Materials and Services available.
We  do not want to receive unsolicited information from you through the Site for the purpose of communicating to our company any ideas or other information, including, but not limited to product or service suggestions or enhancements, product or service names, advertising campaigns or marketing plans, technology or material, business methods, or any similar information. We maintain this policy to prevent misunderstandings or disputes in the event it develops products or services that may seem similar to an unsolicited proposal. Any non-personal unsolicited information or material sent to us will be deemed NOT confidential, and by sending such unsolicited information our company is hereby granted an unrestricted, worldwide, royalty-free, perpetual and irrevocable license to use, reproduce, display, perform, modify, transmit, and distribute those materials or information, and you also agree that we are free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, or techniques that you send to us for any purpose. Personal information, such as names, addresses, telephone numbers, etc., will remain subject to our Privacy Statement.
3. Terms of use
You undertake not to post to or send via the Website any materials that are or could reasonably be construed as: (i) defamatory, libellous, obscene, offensive, abusive, liable to incite racial hatred, discriminatory or blasphemous; (ii) in breach of any obligation of confidence or privacy or any trade secret; (iii) infringing the proprietary rights of any third party or for which you have not obtained all necessary licenses and/or approvals; or (iv) violating any other law.
You also agree not to transmit to or send via the Website any materials which could reasonably be held to constitute or encourage conduct that would be considered a criminal offence, give rise to civil liability, or otherwise be contrary to the law of any country or other competent authority, or infringe the rights of any third party enforceable in any part of the world.
We reserve the right to remove any materials from the Website where it reasonably suspects that such material is prohibited by this Section or is otherwise inappropriate. Notwithstanding the foregoing, you acknowledge that Canon and its resellers have no control over content on the Website provided by other users neither does it purport to monitor the content of the Website to ensure its accuracy, appropriateness or conformity with the principles outlined in these Terms and Conditions.
You must not link to the Website other websites which are indecent or inappropriate, and you must forthwith remove any link if we in our discretion so request.
Materials (including, but not limited to, text, music, sound, photographs, graphics, images, video, data compilations, digital downloads and software) and unless otherwise specified, or third party materials linked and/or referred to on the Website are the property of Canon Production Printing and its business partners and protected by national and international copyright laws.
Copyright of the third party materials will be subject to jurisdictions specified in the third party website.
We authorize you to view and download the Materials, if available, only for your personal, non-commercial, internal use; provided that you do not modify or create any derivative work of the Materials in any way, or reproduce or publicly display, perform, or distribute or otherwise use them for any public or commercial purpose. Any use of the Materials on any other website or networked computer environment for any purpose is prohibited. We reserve the right to revoke the authorization to view, download, and print Materials, available on the Website, at any time, and any such use shall be discontinued immediately upon our notice. The rights granted to you constitute a limited license and not a transfer of title or of any other right or interest in the Services or Materials.
If you wish to use the Services or Materials beyond the scope as authorized above, you need to obtain our prior approval or the relevant copyright owners or licensors of such Materials, i.e. we, our business partners or others respectively. You agree to indemnify Canon Production Printing and its affiliates against any claim, demand, loss or damage suffered as a result of breach of these terms of use.
We do not give authorization for the use of third party materials for any personal and/ or non-commercial use. Authorization for the use of third party materials remains with the relevant third party.
Your access to the Services will be consistent with your business relationship with Canon Production Printing, its subsidiaries, affiliates and resellers. You may use the Services only for the purposes specifically authorized by us. You may not modify or otherwise adulterate the Services and may enter or have entered data only where specified for such purpose.
4. Registration
You may need to activate an account to access the Website. Upon activating your account, you may access and use the Services or Materials available on the Website through an account we may provide for such purpose or through a third party login made available by a third party identity provider. Upon such successful activation, we authorize you to access and use the Website subject to the Terms and Conditions.
You are responsible for use of and maintaining the confidentiality of your account made available by us or your third party login. If needed, strong passwords are encouraged. A strong password is one with upper and lower case letters and numbers. If there is a breach of the confidentiality, or any breach of security through a third party login or account, then you shall notify us immediately using the email address info@cpp.canon. We may cancel, alter or replace any account in its sole discretion at any time.
5. Privacy Statement; Data Collection
To enable your use of the Website, we may collect information about your use of the Website (“Information”). Use and possible transfer of the Information is subject to our Privacy Statement. You agree that the collection and use of Information , and operation and provision of the Website, as contemplated under this Terms and Conditions, is not a breach of your right of privacy, publicity, or any other right related to protection of personal data, whether in equity, law, contract, or otherwise. You hereby waive any and all such claims or rights of action, whether foreseen or unforeseen, so long as the Information is used in accordance with our Privacy Statement or in case of you making use of Materials or Services provided by our subsidiary, affiliate or reseller, the privacy policy of such party.
For the purpose of administering the Services and improving the performance of a Canon product you use, we may from time to time access your content directly relating to the performance of such product in an anonymous way. Such content will be service data and diagnosis data directly relating to the Canon product you use and stored on the Website by activating the Services (“Content”). This information will not contain your end-user information only product performance data. For further information on what type of information and data is retrieved and how access or entry to such information and data by Canon Production Printing and its suppliers (i.e. its subsidiaries, affiliates and/or resellers) is secured please read our Privacy Statement.
We understand that Content, which is automatically stored through activating certain Services or placed in an area of the Website subject to password protection, may contain information that you regard as confidential and proprietary. Although we may have access to those areas for Website administration purposes, we regard such information as the confidential information of you or the entity for which you act. We agree that we shall treat all Content in such areas with the same degree of care as we accord to our own confidential information of a similar nature, but in no event less than reasonable care. Any and all confidential information, which is automatically uploaded through activating certain Services or placed by you in an area of the Site subject to password protection shall remain the property of the entity for which you act, and Canon Production Printing does not acquire any ownership interest in your or such entity’s Content or any patent, copyright, trademark or other intellectual property right by the presence of Content on the Website.
6. Disclaimer
Canon Production Printing hereby excludes all conditions, warranties, representations or other terms concerning the supply or purported supply of, failure to supply or delay in supplying any Material or Service in connection with the Website or that the Website is accurate, complete or up-to-date, which might but for this section 5 have effect between us and you, or would otherwise be implied into or incorporated into these Terms and Conditions or any collateral contract, whether by statute, common law or otherwise. You understand and agree that you are using the Website at your sole risk and that we do not warrant that the Website will meet your requirements or that the Website will be uninterrupted, error free or secure. Any Materials, content or Services provided via the Website or in connection with the Website by us is done so on an “AS IS” and on an “AS AVAILABLE” basis and Canon Production Printing, its subsidiaries, affiliates or resellers make no representations or endorsement of any kind, whether express or implied, with respect to the Website for the Materials, content or Services included in, or made available in connection with, the Website. Canon Production Printing reserves the right at its sole discretion, to amend or withdraw any Materials, content or Services offered as part of the Website.
7. WARRANTIES AND LIABILITY
CANON PRODUCTION PRINTING, ANY OTHER PARTY (WHETHER OR NOT INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING, MAINTAINING OR DELIVERING THIS WEBSITE), AND ANY OF CANON’S GROUP COMPANIES AND THE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, SHAREHOLDERS OR AGENTS OF ANY OF THEM, EXCLUDE ALL LIABILITY AND RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY AMOUNT OR KIND OF LOSS OR DAMAGE THAT MAY RESULT TO YOU OR A THIRD PARTY, (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE OR CONSEQUENTIAL LOSS OR DAMAGES, OR ANY LOSS OF INCOME, PROFITS, GOODWILL, DATA, CONTRACTS, USE OF MONEY, OR LOSS OR DAMAGES ARISING FROM OR CONNECTED IN ANY WAY TO BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, AND WHETHER IN TORT (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION NEGLIGENCE), CONTRACT OR OTHERWISE IN CONNECTION WITH THIS WEBSITE IN ANY WAY OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE, INABILITY TO USE OR THE RESULTS OF USE OF THIS WEBSITE, ANY WEBSITES LINKED TO THIS WEBSITE OR THE MATERIAL OR SERVICE ON SUCH WEBSITES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOSS OR DAMAGE DUE TO VIRUSES THAT MAY INFECT YOUR COMPUTER EQUIPMENT, SOFTWARE, DATA OR OTHER PROPERTY ON ACCOUNT OF YOUR ACCESS TO, USE OF, OR BROWSING THIS WEBSITE OR YOUR DOWNLOADING OF ANY MATERIAL OR USE OF SERVICES FROM THIS WEBSITE OR ANY WEBSITES LINKED TO THIS WEBSITE. THIS SHALL NOT AFFECT YOUR STATUTORY RIGHTS.
THIS WEBSITE MAY CONTAIN LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES THAT ARE NOT UNDER THE CONTROL OF CANON PRODUCTION PRINTING. CANON PRODUCTION PRINTING IS NOT LIABLE FOR THE ACCURACY IN CONTENT AND ADVISORY VALUE OF ANY THIRD PARTY INFORMATION THAT ARE LINKED AND/ OR REFERRED TO IN THE WEBSITE. THE LINKS AND REFERENCE ARE PROVIDED FOR YOUR INFORMATION ONLY AND THE INCLUSION OF SUCH LINKS DOES NOT IMPLY THAT CANON PRODUCTION PRINTING ENDORSES OR ACCEPTS ANY RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE CONTENT OR USES OF SUCH OTHER WEBSITES. WHEN YOU ACCESS AN OTHER WEBSITE, YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK. CANON PRODUCTION PRINTING HAS NO CONTROL OVER THE CONTENTS OF THESE THIRD PARTY SITES AND EXCLUDES ALL LIABILITY AND RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY AMOUNT OR KIND OF LOSS OR DAMAGE THAT MAY RESULT TO YOU OR A THIRD PARTY FOR THE USE OF THESE INFORMATION. NOTHING IN THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SHALL EXCLUDE OR LIMIT OUR LIABILITY FOR (I) DEATH OR PERSONAL INJURY CAUSED BY ITS NEGLIGENCE; (II) FRAUD; OR (III) ANY LIABILITY WHICH CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR LIMITED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW.
8. Trademark
You must not display or use in any manner Canon’s trademarks or logos without Canon’s prior written permission.
9. Governing Law
These Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of The Netherlands. Disputes arising in connection with these Terms and Conditions shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Dutch courts. The application of the U.N. Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods and the Uniform Computer Information Transactions Act (“UCITA”) or any state implementation of the UCITA is expressly excluded. No choice of law rules of any jurisdiction apply.
Copyright
Copyright ©2020 Canon Production Printing. All rights reserved. It is strictly prohibited to copy, redistribute, republish or modify any materials or software contained on the Website or in subsequent support without our prior written consent.
About usPeople and culture
Worldwide
History
Mission and vision
Products & TechnologiesLarge format
Cutsheet
Continuous feed
Technologies
Cookies settings
Decide which cookies you want to allow. You can change these settings at any time. However, this can result in some functions no longer being available.
By selecting an option below you can enable or disable different types of cookies:
Block all
Essentials
Analytics
This website will
Remember your cookie permission settingAllow session cookiesGather information you input into a contact form or other forms across all pages
This website won't
Remember your login detailsRemember social media settingsKeep track of your visited pages and interaction takenKeep track about your location and region based on your IP numberKeep track of the time spent on each pageIncrease the data quality of the statistics functionsTailor information and advertising to your interests based on e.g. the content you have visited before. (Currently we do not use targeting or targeting cookies)Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website will
Essential: Remember your cookie permission settingEssential: Allow session cookiesEssential: Gather information you input into a contact forms newsletter and other forms across all pagesFunctionality: Remember social media settingsFunctionality: Remember selected region and country
This website won't
Analytics: Keep track of your visited pages and interaction takenAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Keep track of the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Increase the data quality of the statistics functionsAdvertising: Tailor information and advertising to your interests based on e.g. the content you have visited before. (Currently we do not use targeting or targeting cookies)Advertising: Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website will
Remember your cookie permission settingAllow session cookiesGather information you input into a contact form or other forms across all pagesKeep track of your visited pages and interaction takenKeep track about your location and region based on your IP numberKeep track of the time spent on each pageIncrease the data quality of the statistics functions
This website won't
Tailor information and advertising to your interests based on e.g. the content you have visited before. (Currently we do not use targeting or targeting cookies)Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website will
Functionality: Remember social media settingsFunctionality: Remember selected region and countryAnalytics: Keep track of your visited pages and interaction takenAnalytics: Keep track about your location and region based on your IP numberAnalytics: Keep track of the time spent on each pageAnalytics: Increase the data quality of the statistics functionsAdvertising: Tailor information and advertising to your interests based on e.g. the content you have visited before. (Currently we do not use targeting or targeting cookies)Advertising: Gather personally identifiable information such as name and location
This website won't
Remember your login details
Save & close
